Gaoxing, once we go, there's no turning back.
غاوشينغ، بمجرد أن نذهب، لن يكون هناك عودة إلى الوراء.
If you still have any secrets,
إذا كان لا يزال لديك أي أسرار،
it's not too late to tell us now.
ليس من المتأخر أن تخبرنا الآن.
You're overthinking it.
أنت تفكر في الأمر أكثر من اللازم.
I'm just an ordinary person.
أنا مجرد شخص عادي.
What secrets could I possibly have?
ما هي الأسرار التي من الممكن أن أملكها؟
So calm.
هادئ جداً.
Doesn't seem like he's lying to us.
لا يبدو أنه يكذب علينا.
No rush. You'll know once we get there.
لا داعي للعجلة، ستعرف حالما نصل.
Hello, Mom.
مرحبا أمي.
We're already on our way.
نحن في طريقنا بالفعل.
Make a nice dinner tonight.
حضّر عشاءً لطيفًا الليلة.
Okay, son.
حسنًا يا ابني.
I'll have dinner ready and wait for you.
سأعد العشاء وأنتظرك.
This is today's new script.
هذا هو النص الجديد لليوم.
Everyone, memorize your lines quickly.
الجميع، احفظوا سطوركم بسرعة.
Do your best later.
افعل ما بوسعك لاحقًا.
Once we're done,
بمجرد الانتهاء،
everyone will get paid.
الجميع سيحصلون على أجرهم.
Okay.
تمام.
Nightingale, you've worked hard lately.
يا نايتنجيل، لقد عملت بجد في الآونة الأخيرة.
This task,
هذه المهمة،
let me handle it.
دعني أتعامل مع الأمر.
You?
أنت؟
Yeah, since the boss is so interested,
نعم، بما أن الرئيس مهتم جدًا،
I'll join in and play along too.
سأشارك وألعب أيضًا.
Then you'd better hold back a little.
إذن من الأفضل أن تتراجع قليلاً.
Don't mess things up for the boss.
لا تفسد الأمور على رئيسك.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Leave it to me.
اتركها لي.
We're here. This is my hometown.
نحن هنا. هذه مدينتي.
This is Qingshui Village.
هذه قرية تشينغشوي.
It's the countryside, so it's a bit rundown.
إنها منطقة ريفية، لذا فهي مهجورة بعض الشيء.
Can't compare to the big city.
لا يمكن مقارنتها بالمدينة الكبيرة.
If you're not used to it,
إذا لم تكن معتادًا على ذلك،
It's still not too late to go back now.
لم يفت الأوان بعد للعودة الآن.
No need, since we're already here.
لا داعي لذلك، لأننا هنا بالفعل.
There's no reason to turn back halfway.
ليس هناك سبب للعودة إلى منتصف الطريق.
Let's go, let's take a look.
دعنا نذهب، دعنا نلقي نظرة.
This kid, Xiao Gao,
هذا الطفل، شياو جاو،
has been sensible since he was little.
لقد كان عاقلاً منذ أن كان صغيراً.
As soon as he learned to walk,
بمجرد أن تعلم المشي،
bare-bottomed,
عاري المؤخرة،
he already knew to come help out at home.
لقد كان يعلم بالفعل أنه يجب عليه أن يأتي للمساعدة في المنزل.
Having such a considerate and responsible kid as a husband
أن يكون لديك طفل متفهم ومسؤول كزوج
is really your good fortune, girl.
هل هذا حقا حظك السعيد يا فتاة؟
Xiao Gao has been smart since he was young.
لقد كان شياو جاو ذكيًا منذ صغره.
He studies hard and is exceptionally talented.
إنه يدرس بجد وهو موهوب بشكل استثنائي.
Back then, I already thought
في ذلك الوقت، كنت أعتقد بالفعل
this boy would definitely make something of himself.
هذا الصبي بالتأكيد سوف يصنع شيئا لنفسه.
He's truly extraordinary.
إنه استثنائي حقا.
Whoever marries him
من يتزوجه
is sure to have a good life.
من المؤكد أن لديك حياة جيدة.
Xiao Gao, this kid
شياو جاو، هذا الطفل
Ah
اه
No, I mean Brother Gaoxing
لا، أقصد الأخ غاوشينغ
He's always been especially nice to us since we were little
لقد كان لطيفًا معنا دائمًا منذ أن كنا صغارًا
He was the leader of the kids in our area
لقد كان قائدًا للأطفال في منطقتنا
All the girls in our village used to say
كانت جميع الفتيات في قريتنا يقولون
They wanted to marry him when they grew up
لقد أرادوا الزواج منه عندما يكبرون
Brother Gaoxing
الأخ غاوشينغ
Which of these two sisters is your wife?
من بين هاتين الأختين من هي زوجتك؟
Silly, only kids make choices
سخيف، فقط الأطفال هم من يتخذون القرارات
Of course Brother Gaoxing wants them all
بالطبع الأخ جاوشينغ يريدهم جميعا
Don't talk nonsense
لا تتحدث هراء
Go play, you two
اذهبا للعب، أنتما الاثنان
Kids say the darndest things
الأطفال يقولون أشياء غريبة
I didn't expect that
لم اتوقع ذلك
People in your village think highly of you
الناس في قريتك يفكرون فيك بشكل كبير
Can't help it, our village is just simple and honest
لا يمكننا مساعدة أنفسنا، قريتنا بسيطة وصادقة
Everyone likes to speak the truth
الجميع يحب أن يقول الحقيقة
It's getting late
لقد تأخر الوقت
There's food made at home
هناك طعام مصنوع في المنزل
Let's go back and see my parents
دعونا نعود ونرى والدي
Okay, lead the way
حسنًا، قم بقيادة الطريق
Dad
أب
Mom
أم
I'm back!
لقد عدت!
Gaoxing is back!
جاوشينغ عاد!
Come in quickly.
ادخل بسرعة.
Which one of these two is it?
أي واحد من هذين هو؟
Su Qingyan, your daughter-in-law.
سو تشينغيان، زوجة ابنك.
Oh, okay.
أوه، حسنا.
This is her best friend.
هذه هي صديقتها المفضلة.
A bonus, buy one get one free.
مكافأة، اشتري واحدة واحصل على واحدة مجانًا.
Who's the "buy one get one free"?
من هو صاحب العرض "اشتري واحد واحصل على واحد مجانًا"؟
Hello, Uncle and Auntie.
مرحباً عمي وعمتي.
Why call us Uncle and Auntie?
لماذا نطلق علينا اسم العم والعمة؟
Just like Gaoxing.
تمامًا مثل جاوشينغ.
Just call us Mom and Dad.
فقط اتصل بنا أمي وأبي.
Mom, Dad.
أمي، أبي.
Yes, yes, good.
نعم نعم جيد.
Such a beautiful girl
فتاة جميلة جدا
is actually our family's daughter-in-law.
هي في الواقع زوجة ابن عائلتنا.
Gaoxing,
غاوكسينغ،
you're really lucky.
أنت محظوظ حقا.
Well,
حسنًا،
everyone must be hungry.
لا بد أن الجميع جائعون.
Your mom and I will go bring out the food.
أنا وأمك سنذهب لإحضار الطعام.
Go on, go on, go on.
إستمر، إستمر، إستمر.
Let's go, let's go.
دعنا نذهب، دعنا نذهب.
Your parents are really warm and welcoming.
والدتك ودودين ومرحبين حقًا.
Of course they are.
بالطبع هم كذلك.
When they heard you were coming,
عندما سمعوا بقدومك،
they got up early to start cooking.
استيقظوا مبكرًا لبدء الطبخ.
You're really from Qingshui Village?
هل أنت حقا من قرية تشينغشوي؟
Everything in the documents is true.
كل ما هو موجود في الوثائق صحيح.
What else would it be?
ماذا سيكون غير ذلك؟
Are you doubting me?
هل تشك بي؟
Sorry about that.
آسف على ذلك.
Actually, we originally came here to...
في الواقع، لقد أتينا إلى هنا في الأصل من أجل...
Honey.
عسل.
Honey
عسل
Honey, you're finally back.
عزيزتي، لقد عدت أخيرا.
You were working in the city,
كنت تعمل في المدينة،
leaving me all alone at home.
تركني وحدي في المنزل.
I missed you so much.
لقد افتقدتك كثيرا.
Happy
سعيد
Explain to me clearly who she is.
اشرح لي بوضوح من هي.
Her?
ها؟
I'm his wife. Who are you two?
أنا زوجته. من أنتما الإثنان؟
What a joke.
يا لها من مزحة!
If you're his wife, then what does that make our Qingyan?
إذا كنت زوجته، فما الذي يجعل هذا تشينغيان لدينا؟
What does she have to do with me?
ما علاقتها بي؟
Honey
عسل
How did you go out and come back with two women?
كيف خرجت ورجعت مع امرأتين؟
If you keep this up, I'll get jealous.
إذا واصلت على هذا المنوال، سأشعر بالغيرة.
Alright, happy.
حسنا، سعيد.
I was about to say I misunderstood you.
كنت على وشك أن أقول أنني أساءت فهمك.
I didn't expect you to have a wife here.
لم أتوقع أن يكون لك زوجة هنا.
No wonder you kept making excuses not to bring us back.
لا عجب أنك واصلت تقديم الأعذار لعدم إعادتنا.
So you were hiding a woman here all along.
إذن كنت تخفي امرأة هنا طوال الوقت.
Mr. Gao, do you have anything else to say?
السيد جاو، هل لديك أي شيء آخر لتقوله؟
It's all a misunderstanding.
كل هذا مجرد سوء فهم.
You two wait for me a moment.
انتظروني لحظة.
I asked Nightingale to find someone to put on an act.
لقد طلبت من نايتنجيل أن يجد شخصًا ليقوم بهذا التمثيل.
Why are you making things more complicated?
لماذا تجعل الأمور أكثر تعقيدا؟
I just thought this was a rare opportunity.
اعتقدت أن هذه كانت فرصة نادرة.
So I wanted to have some fun too. How was my performance?
أردتُ أن أستمتع أيضًا. كيف كان أدائي؟
You’re something else, Gao.
أنت شيء آخر، جاو.
Right in front of Qingyan,
مباشرة أمام تشينغيان،
you’re still flirting with another woman.
مازلت تغازل امرأة أخرى.
Have you no shame?
هل ليس لديك خجل؟
An’an, let’s go.
أنآن، دعنا نذهب.
Honey,
عسل،
you’ve misunderstood.
لقد أساءت الفهم.
She’s my sister.
إنها أختي.
She was just joking with you.
لقد كانت تمزح معك فقط.
Sister.
أخت.
She’s the real deal.
إنها الصفقة الحقيقية.
Absolutely genuine.
حقيقية تماما.
My biological sister.
أختي البيولوجية.
Why are you just standing there?
لماذا تقف هناك فقط؟
Hurry up and help me wrap this up.
اسرع وساعدني في إنهاء هذا الأمر.
I can help.
انا استطيع المساعدة.
But I want a raise.
ولكنني أريد زيادة.
Fifty percent.
خمسين بالمئة.
Taking advantage of the situation, huh?
استغلال الوضع، أليس كذلك؟
Thirty percent at most.
ثلاثين بالمئة على الأكثر.
Forget it, then.
انسي الأمر إذن.
I’ll just keep pretending to be your wife.
سأستمر في التظاهر بأنني زوجتك.
Qingyan, look!
تشينغيان، انظر!
Those two shameless people
هذين الشخصين الوقحين
are still flirting and getting handsy.
ما زالوا يغازلون ويتبادلون القبلات.
They’re really treating us like fools.
إنهم يعاملوننا حقًا مثل الحمقى.
Let’s go.
دعنا نذهب.
Honey!
عسل!
You drive a hard bargain.
أنت تقود صفقة صعبة.
Fifty percent it is.
خمسين بالمئة هو كذلك.
You're generous, boss.
أنت كريم يا رئيس.
Deal.
اتفاق.
Sister-in-law, I was just joking with you.
أخت زوجي، كنت أمزح معك فقط.
My name is Gao Qing.
اسمي هو قاو تشينغ.
My brother is right.
أخي على حق.
I really am his sister.
أنا أخته حقا.
You two
انتما الاثنان
are really siblings?
هل هم أشقاء حقا؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Really.
حقًا.
Truer than gold.
أصدق من الذهب.
The food is here!
الطعام هنا!
Qingqing, you're back.
تشينغتشينغ، لقد عدت.
Hurry, hurry, set the table, it's time to eat.
اسرعوا، اسرعوا، جهزوا الطاولة، لقد حان وقت الأكل.
Sister-in-law, come eat.
أخت الزوجة، تعالي وتناولي الطعام.
Come on.
تعال.
Qingyan, try this.
تشينغيان، جرب هذا.
Eat more.
تناول المزيد من الطعام.
Thank you, Mom.
شكرا لك أمي.
We're all family.
نحن جميعا عائلة.
No need to thank me.
لا داعي لشكرني.
Our Gao Xing has a simple nature.
لدى Gao Xing طبيعة بسيطة.
He's very honest.
إنه صادق جداً.
In the future, as you live together,
في المستقبل، كما تعيشون معًا،
please be more understanding.
من فضلك كن أكثر تفهما.
Simple-minded
بسيط التفكير
Very honest
صادق جداً
Are you talking about him?
هل تتحدث عنه؟
My brother is quietly talented.
أخي موهوب بهدوء.
Don’t be fooled by his ordinary appearance.
لا تنخدع بمظهره العادي.
In fact,
في الحقيقة،
his abilities are beyond what you can imagine.
قدراته تفوق ما يمكنك تخيله.
Sister-in-law,
أخت الزوج أو اخت الزوجة،
you’ll be really lucky after marrying my brother.
سوف تكونين محظوظة حقًا بعد الزواج من أخي.
It’s unimaginable.
إنه أمر لا يمكن تصوره.
This delivery guy
هذا الرجل الذي يقوم بالتوصيل
probably makes several thousand a month.
ربما يجني عدة آلاف شهريًا.
Unlike our Qingyan,
على عكس تشينغيان لدينا،
who started a company at such a young age.
الذي بدأ شركة في مثل هذا السن الصغير.
As for her net worth,
أما بالنسبة لثروتها الصافية،
it’s just
إنه فقط
a few hundred million.
بضع مئات الملايين.
A few hundred million—is that a lot?
بضع مئات الملايين - هل هذا كثير؟
Not much, but it’s better than delivering food.
ليس كثيرًا، لكنه أفضل من توصيل الطعام.
Oh, you probably don’t know.
أوه، ربما لا تعرف.
Someone like our Qingyan,
شخص مثل تشينغيان لدينا،
in all of Yuncheng,
في جميع أنحاء يونتشنغ،
all the outstanding young men
جميع الشباب المتميزين
are waiting for her to choose them.
في انتظارها لتختارهم.
Marrying your brother so early
الزواج من أخيك في وقت مبكر جدًا
is really marrying beneath her.
هو في الواقع يتزوج من تحتها.
Oh, then you probably don’t know either.
أوه، إذن ربما لا تعرف أيضًا.
My brother’s admirers
معجبين أخي
line up from here all the way to England.
اصطفوا من هنا حتى إنجلترا.
Even the British princess
حتى الأميرة البريطانية
cries and begs to marry my brother.
تبكي وتتوسل للزواج من أخي.
She’d have to change her nationality first
سيتعين عليها تغيير جنسيتها أولاً
and then line up at the counter for a number.
ثم اصطفوا أمام المنضدة للحصول على رقم.
A female CEO marrying my brother
رئيسة تنفيذية تتزوج أخي
is really marrying up.
هو الزواج فعلا.
Who are you saying is marrying up?
من تقول أنه يتزوج؟
Who are you saying is marrying beneath themselves?
من تقول أنه يتزوج من أدنى منهم؟
Alright, alright, stop arguing.
حسنًا، حسنًا، توقف عن الجدال.
Let’s eat, let’s eat.
دعونا نأكل، دعونا نأكل.
How about we open a bottle of wine?
ماذا عن فتح زجاجة نبيذ؟
Let's all have a drink.
دعونا جميعا نشرب.
Oh, no, no.
أوه، لا، لا.
I don't drink alcohol.
انا لا اشرب الكحول.
I'm driving, so I can't drink.
أنا أقود السيارة، لذلك لا أستطيع الشرب.
If they won't drink, we will.
إذا لم يشربوا، فسنشرب نحن.
Meeting Qingqing today,
لقاء تشينغتشينغ اليوم،
it feels like we've known each other forever.
أشعر وكأننا نعرف بعضنا البعض منذ زمن طويل.
We have to have a drink.
علينا أن نشرب.
Qingqing, you're not scared, are you?
تشينغتشينغ، أنت لست خائفًا، أليس كذلك؟
An'an, you're joking.
أنآن، أنت تمزح.
It's rare for me to be in such a good mood.
من النادر أن أكون في مزاج جيد كهذا.
As your big sister, I'll keep you company to the end.
باعتباري أختك الكبرى، سأبقيك برفقتي حتى النهاية.
How's it going downstairs?
كيف تسير الأمور في الطابق السفلي؟
An'an and your sister are having a drinking contest.
أنان وأختك لديهما مسابقة شرب.
The two of them are really getting into it.
إنهما ينخرطان في الأمر حقًا.
My sister is spoiled.
أختي مدللة.
Please don't mind her.
من فضلك لا تهتم بها.
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
Actually, we were the ones being presumptuous.
في الواقع، نحن الذين كنا مفترضين.
We came over without letting them know first.
لقد أتينا دون أن نخبرهم أولاً.
But your uncle and aunt are really nice.
لكن عمك وعمتك لطيفين حقًا.
Of course, they're professionals.
بالطبع، إنهم محترفون.
Ah.
اه.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
I just meant the environment here is pretty simple.
أعني فقط أن البيئة هنا بسيطة جدًا.
As long as you don't mind.
طالما أنك لا تمانع.
Not at all, I actually like it here.
لا على الإطلاق، أنا في الواقع أحب هذا المكان.
It's warm and peaceful.
إنه دافئ وهادئ.
The people are honest and kind.
الناس صادقون و طيبون.
It's not like our Yun City.
إنها ليست مثل مدينتنا يون.
Every day is just work and scheming against others.
كل يوم هو مجرد عمل وتخطيط ضد الآخرين.
By the way, about the skincare products last time—
بالمناسبة، بخصوص منتجات العناية بالبشرة في المرة الماضية—
I haven't properly thanked you yet.
لم أشكرك بشكل صحيح بعد.
Just another verbal thank you?
مجرد شكر لفظي آخر؟
Can't you give me a real reward for once?
هل يمكنك أن تعطيني مكافأة حقيقية هذه المرة؟
Who says I don't have one?
من قال أنني لا أملك واحدة؟